https://www.polypeptide.com/confidentiality-policy/

Confidentiality PolicyHome Confidentiality Policy
Confidentiality Policy
We respect the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy is designed to help you understand what information we gather from our Web site and what we do with that information. Because we will continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features we provide on our Web site, this policy is subject to change without prior notice. For that reason, we encourage you to review the Privacy Policy periodically. By using our Web site, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy in effect at that time.
Information Sharing
PolyPeptide Group is the sole owner of any information collected on this Web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. PolyPeptide Group may collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
We intend to give you as much control as reasonably possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit www.PolyPeptide.com without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times when we may need information from you in order to service your needs. If you choose to give us personal information we may use that information to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with requested materials, for example. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact, we will respect your wishes. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then discard it.
Logging Site Traffic
PolyPeptide Group maintains log files of the site traffic on www.PolyPeptide.com. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personal information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads, identify the content most commonly accessed, and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types.
Cookies
Cookies can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. This Web site uses “cookies” so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully utilize all features of this Web site. You have the ability to delete cookie files from your hard drive at any time.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Web site. Your use of this site constitutes acceptance of our policy. If you do not agree to the terms, please exit from this site immediately.
Création, hébergement et référencement du site Internet
ID Interactive – Création site internet professionnel
ID Interactive SAS au capital de 23 000 euros
SIRET : 490 491 594 00019
CODE APE : 6201Z
TVA IC : FR23490491594
Siège social :
Parc d’activités de Doaren Molac 2
56 610 Arradon- Morbihan
Téléphone : +33 (0)2 97 69 07 43
Fax : +33 (0)2 97 47 64 31
Email : contact@id-interactive.fr
Site web : https://www.id-interactive.fr
© Confidentiality 2018 PolyPeptide Group • Cookie management • Personal data • Sitemap
ACTH (1-39) PorcineAtosibanCalcitoninCarbetocinDeslorelinDesmopressinExenatideFelypressinGonadorelin Acetate / HCILeuprolideLiraglutideOctreotidePTH (1-34) TeriparatideSemaglutideSomatostatinTriptorelinVasopressin, 8-L-Arginine
By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies on our website . However you may visit Cookie Settings to provide a controlled consent.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
You can enable or disable your consent for each category of cookie.
More information on the collection of personal data
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
The necessary cookies help to make a website usable by enabling basic functions such as page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Advertisement
advertisement
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors through websites. The goal is to display ads that are relevant and interesting to the individual user and therefore more valuable to third-party publishers and advertisers.
Analytics
analytics
Statistical cookies help website owners, through the anonymous collection and communication of information, to understand how visitors interact with websites.
Performance
performance
Preferences cookies allow a website to retain information that changes the way the site behaves or displays, such as your preferred language or the region in which you are located.
Save & Accept
COVID-19 Outbreak Information –
Click here for the latest updates
